Hello everyone, welcome to The Real Investor channel.
Today we are going to talk
about the quarter four results of ICICI Lo and the dividend announced by them.
So
we will talk further about how much dividend will be given on the shares.  Before that,
if you are new to the channel then like,
subscribe and share the channel so that you keep
getting all the updates in the future.  So
let us talk about ICICI LB.  The
net profit of ICICI LBA for quarter 4 has
increased by about 7%, which was
earlier ₹47 crores and a
premium growth of 17% was also seen and
you can see that they have also announced a dividend of ₹7.  Let us
move ahead and see
what their future holds and if we
talk about the previous quarter or the
same quarter of the previous year, if we talk about the previous year
or talk about the total,
here you can see that
their revenue in the December quarter of last year was Rs
600, sorry, if we talk about the March quarter, then the
revenue was Rs 61 crore and
if we talk about the profit, then the profit was Rs 510 crore, the
current profit is Rs 5,
you can see here that the profit is Rs 547 crore
and
we also talk about the premium.  Let
us see it in detail further and if you want this full detail
video then please comment so that
I can bring full detail videos for you in future.  There is a
year on year rise of 177.25 here.  The profit for the
quarter was Rs 547 crore compared to the previous
quarter of the same year, which was Rs 510
crore.  It was worth Rs 510 crore.  If we
talk about profit before tax, which has
increased by Rs 700.18
crore, which has increased
from Rs 668 crore to Rs 700 crore, then
if we talk about profit before tax in crores, then
here you can see that in 25
itself, here the profit before tax is at Rs
3659.
Here you can see that if we
talk about operating profit, then there was
an increase of 31.3% in operating profit which has happened
from Rs 546 crore and
if we look at the corresponding quarters of the previous quarter, then it was Rs
46 crore.  So the
underwriting losses of all these things is Rs
282 crore.  Compared to the
previous year, there was a loss of
0.29%. If we talk about one year, the combined
ratio improved to 111.2%
from 112.5% ​​on a year-on-year basis.
If we talk about gross direct premium income, then
that too has seen an increase.
Which is a
very good growth of 18% reflective in quarter four.  The
industry growth is
10% but its growth is
18%, almost double.
So this is a very good thing.  Here, if we
talk about excluding
growth, then
we have excluded the mass health segment in this
and if GDPI, which is their gross
direct premium income growth, is 18% compared
to the industry growth of 13%, then
this company is doing quite well.  If you
liked the video, please like,
subscribe and share the channel so that you can
get more such videos in the future.
Thank you.